(Sheldon:)Yeah, take whatever you want.
(Leonard:)I would like to keep...
(Leonard:)the official flag
of our apartment.
(Sheldon:)But you don't even like flags.
(Leonard:)Yeah, I like this one.
(Sheldon:)But I designed it.
(Leonard:)But you made me order it because
you were "too well-known"
(Leonard:)in the flag community
and they'd jack up the price.
(Sheldon:)But you don't even understand
(Sheldon:)- its symbolism.
- Oh, I do.
The-the field of blue
represents you being miserable,
(Leonard:)and the lion sticking
its tongue out means
(Leonard:)I'm happy about it.
(Sheldon:)Come along, Amy.
(Sheldon:)I know when I'm not wanted.
(Amy:)I don't think you do,
but all right.
(Bernadette:)Stuart, you cooked?
(Howard:)How did you know it wasn't me?
(Bernadette:)There's only three
people in this house,
(Bernadette:)and you'd still be
my fifth guess.